Hashmatullah Afroz

UK, Hayward heath, The Priory

+447860194058 | zaherhashmatullah I @gmail.com

OBJECTIVE -

I am an experienced software developer. I bring more than five years' experience writing PHP full-stack applications, JavaScript, Django and more than three years' experience in the technology industry. Due to my qualification, extensive background, training, I am interested to apply for the vacant position and join your respected team. That will be really kind of you if you do a closer look at the particulars of my education and skills which you find on my CV. I am very confident of Management, Supervision, Monitoring, evaluation, Coordinating, reporting, Analyzing, interpreting, team work, have good speaking voice, neat and respectable appearance, Ability and willingness of working outside normal office hours

EXPERIENCE -

2016 - 2016

Teacher

Azerakhsh Academic Centre

English literature, 10 month program for teaching English Language

2016 - 2017

Invigilator

British Council Control and organize candidates during exam day

2018 - 2020

· Customer care

AWCC (Afghan Wireless Communication Centre)

Greeting the customers offer them credit cards and also, I was selling the cards in one side

2021 - 2022

Freelancer

Diamond Gym

I developed a CMS for the gym, it was a localhost database and I was maintain the database for them

2022 - Up to Now

· Full stack Web Developer

AM&M (Accelerated Mail& Marketing)

Ima full stack web developer in the company i am developing website for the clients and making secure and updating the websites, Ima administrating the databases and doing IT works like upgrading windows, configuration of new PC with the network Ima also working with active directories creating users and managing them.

EDUCATION -

2015 - 2016

· Azerakhsh Academic Centre

English literature

2017

· Habibya High School

2019

. Udemy site

Web Programming Languages

2018 - 2022

Bakhtar Unversity

Computer Science, Software Engineering

SKILLS

- Basics of C/C++ programming language
- C# Programming language game development (Unity)
- Basics of Java Programming Language
- lavaScript (Full-Stack Developer)
- Basics of Python Programming Language
- FRONT-END Web development HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, React.JS
- BACK-END(Server) Development: PHP Laravel, PDO Paradigm, PHP (Magento), Node.js (Express.JS), MVC pattern, Basics of Django (python) MVT pattern
- * DATABASE Development : MySQL(RDBMS), MongoDB(non-relational), SQLlite3(RDBMS)
- * Mobile Development : React-Native(JavaScript) IOS and Android
- Networking and reconnaissance (PT) Familiar with Linux OS

Gym Management

Manipulating data, creating reports, Authorization, authentication and much more

Restaurant

Creating reports, Analyzing Data, manipulating data and so on

· My portfolio

You can check my portfolio here. https://hashmatullahafroz.github.io/Hashmatullah-Afroz-portfolio

https://github.com/HashmatullahAfroz

You can check my skills in my LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/hashmatullah-afroz-0a53a0249

LANGUAGES -

- Farsi
- Pashto
- English
- Urdu
- Arabic

REFERENCE -

• Bezhan Rasuly - AWCC

Team Leader

+93700801773